KLYMENKO ALINA



Contacts

Alina2Kl

in Alina Klymenko

🌭 +38 (068) 114-75-25

Languages

- Ukrainian
- English

Summary

I graduated with a degree in non-technical specialties, but always had a great interest in programming and creating video games. I have a great desire to master the profession of Frontend developer and put a lot of effort and time into it. I hope that a good experience in graphic design will help me create usability and beautiful products.

Skills

HTML MySQL React CSS Git/GitHub JavaScript

Experience

· Content Management Specialist, Digital Marketing Manager at Quadrasoft

November 2018 - March 2022

Job Responsibilities: Producing and publishing content for mypharmacy.com.ua (photo processing, writing unique texts, graphic design), Database working, Internal and external SEO optimization, SMM management, Linkbuilding, E-mail marketing, Tracking web analytics.

• Content Management Specialist, Junior PPC Specialist at PE Ponochovnyi

November 2017 - October 2018

Job Responsibilities: Producing and publishing content for sites bano.pro, mario.in.ua (photo processing, writing unique texts, graphic design), Internal and external SEO optimization, PPC (Google Ads), Database working in 1C: Enterprise, E-mail marketing.

· Content Management Specialist at Watermart

November 2016 - September 2017

Job Responsibilities: Producing and publishing content for watermart.ua and myspa.com.ua, Processing photos, Copywriting, E-mail marketing.

· Content Management Specialist at Sitius Service

May 2016 - November 2016

Job Responsibilities: Producing and publishing content for plitka.ua (CMS Bitrix), Updating prices and availability of goods in 1C: Enterprise, Copywriting, Graphic design.

Education

PhD of ecology - 2015 Institute of Agroecology and Nature management NAAS, Ukraine

Master of ecology - 2010 V.I. Vernadsky Taurida National University, Ukraine